Contact

amitbd595@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amitbiswas-tm (LinkedIn)

www.getmore7.com (Blog)

Top Skills

Web Development

Web Design

WordPress Design

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Bangla (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Fundamentals of digital marketing

Amit Biswas ™#

Advance WordPress Theme Developer || Web Designer || Digital Marketing Expert.

Chattogram

Summary

Hello, I am a web designer & skillful WordPress theme developer. I have 5+ years of experience in web development and completed 200+ online & offline courses. Expert at converting PSD to responsive HTML design or WordPress theme, Customize any kind of WordPress theme & fix any kind of WordPress bugs.

My Skill:

For WordPress Theme Development:

Converting HTML to WordPress theme.

Custom function create.

Custom condition set

Create a WordPress child theme.

Convert your theme as like ThemeForest's original theme.

The user manual gives for next time you can change any section.

For WordPress Theme Customize:

Create WordPress landing page.

Theme customization.

E-Commerce website.

woocommerce function.

Speed optimization.

Website migration.

Popup page, Offer page, Hero page, Contact form & any issue.

Demo input, WordPress install, Email account, E-commerce payment gateway, Product Upload, Backup file.

For WordPress Bug / Error Fix:

Install WordPress issue.

Install any Plugin and active issue fix.

Theme menu style issue fix.

Any HTML coding issue.

Fix PHP, Jquery issue.

Fix any theme-related issues.

Plugin setup-related issues.

Any CSS coding issue.

Mobile Responsive issue fix.

landing page, Hero page, Popup page issue.

WordPress speed optimization setup or any issue fix. (CDN Setup)

Any layout change or any bug fix.

WordPress login issue fix.

404 Issue.

WordPress Live Stream setup.

Auto-Update any issue.

And More #

For Web Design:

100% mobile responsive website template create.

Convert PSD to Responsive HTML file.

Awesome knowledge of HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap.

Do create all single page ar multipage web template.

For Digital Marketing:

Facebook paid ads set for your WordPress eCommerce or Shopify store Products. (100% Analysis targeted country, age, interest, and retarget old customer.)

Facebook business manager control.

Google paid ads set.

On-page SEO, Off-page SEO.

Content writing.

Facebook marketing.

Lead generation.

Email Marketing.

SEO Backlinks.

Experience

Fiverr

5 years 2 months

Wordpress Developer and SEO Specialist June 2018 - Present (3 years 2 months) Bangladesh

Web Designer
January 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months)
Bangladesh

Best for your business.

Web Developer June 2016 - Present (5 years 2 months) Israel

Graphic Designer August 2017 - Present (4 years)

Google

6 years 4 months

Search Engine Optimization Specialist April 2015 - Present (6 years 4 months)

On Page SEO
July 2016 - Present (5 years 1 month)

Google Top Ranking
May 2015 - Present (6 years 3 months)

LinkedIn
Lead Generation
October 2016 - Present (4 years 10 months)

Mailchimp Email Marketing Specialist August 2016 - Present (5 years)

JVZoo Affiliate Marketing Specialist June 2017 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Linkedin = Facebook Social Media Marketing Specialist April 2016 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Getmo Webflow Wordpress Developer April 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 6 months) United States

Did somebody say incredible ultra conversion focus website?

Well, this is your lucky day, my name is Incredible Web, haha just kidding

My name is Amit Biswas, and I am here to design the web of your dreams, but also a web that actually convert and sell with the best User Experience practices

I have more than 5 years of experience doing websites, first with code, and now with builders (Divi, Elementor, beaver, etc)

The good news is: I still have the coding knowledge, and now I am an experienced designer too, so I have 2 superpowers, design and coding skills

HERE IS WHAT IS INCLUDED FOR YOU:

- Web design
- Webpage mobile optimization
- plugins set up
- Web user experience optimization
- WordPress installation
- Hosting set up
- Hosting and websites migration
- SSL certification set up

EXTRA:

- Site speed optimization
- Copywriting and creative content creation adapted to your brand and business

I CAN SET THE FOLLOWING PREMIUM PLUGINS:

Give donation

Yoast SEO premium

Responsive menu

tutor LMS and learn dash

Smart slider and revolution slider

Elementor

analytics

DIVI SPACE

DIVI SUPREME

DIVI MONK

DIVI PIXEL

Education

National University | Bangladesh

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Accounting · (2017 - 2019)

Government Hazi Mohammad Mohsin College

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Accounting · (2016 - 2018)